what is going on everybody I'm pretty good Halloween boys for a homie coming
每个人都在发生什么事我很漂亮 一个好朋友来的好万圣节男孩
up I have to keep that voice around alright Bucky get off track already ten
起来， 我要 保持这种声音在 好吧巴基 下车轨道已经 十岁 了
seconds in so let's focus on the tutorial well I'm going to teach you
所以让我们专注于 教程我会教 你
guys in this video is how to get the minimum the maximum of a dictionary and
这个视频中的人是如何得到的 最小字典的最大值 和
also how to sort the entire dictionary so it's nice me and in order now you
还有如何 对整个字典进行排序 所以这对我来说很好，现在为了你
guys may be thinking that there's some really easy function that's already built into Python to allow you do this
伙计们可能会认为有一些 非常简单的功能已经存在 内置到Python中 以允许您执行此操作
in a simple kind of way but unfortunately for us there is not and
在一个简单的一种 方式，但 不幸的是，我们 没有和
it's not really intuitive to figure out at first so that's why I want to make
弄清楚它并不是很直观 起初 这就是我想做的原因
this tutorial it's going to save you guys a bunch of time in you probably
本教程将为您节省开支 伙计们 大概是 你们的一大堆时间
want to do this every time you work with dictionary so hohoho that wasn't me um
希望这个 和你一起工作 ， 每次做 字典所以hohoho不是我的 嗯
so I'm going to have to blame it one on someone else all right so the first
所以我将不得不责备它 别人没事 所以第一
thing we need is a dictionary so I'm just going to make mine out of pretend stock prices that I'm just going to pull
我们需要的是字典，所以我 只是想让我的假装出来 我要拉的股票价格
off the top of my head and we'll say that we have like five companies or
在我的头顶，我们会说 我们有像 五家公司 或
something now I know the ticker symbol for Google is goog and this one uses
现在我知道了自动收报机的符号 谷歌是谷歌，这个使用
trades for like five hundred twenty bucks and just make something else I
交易就像五百二十 雄鹿，只是做点别的我
know Facebook FB like 76 54 45 whatever Yahoo I do know this one to UM say this one is like 39 28 and what's another one
知道Facebook FB就像76 54 45一样 雅虎我知道这个 给UM 说这个 一个像39 28，另一个是另一个
I know Amazon and Apple and that's it so Amazon that's not it AMZN on this one is actually pretty expensive around like
我知道亚马逊和苹果，就是这样 亚马逊 不是这个AMZN就是这个 其实蛮贵的 周围像
three hundred five dollars usually an Apple AAPL that's the last one I know
通常是三百五十美元 Apple AAPL 是 我认识 的 最后一个
that is as far as my financial knowledge goes it's somewhere around 100 bucks so
这就是 我的财务知识 它的价格大约在100美元左右
this is a dictionary of course these aren't accurate values but it's good
这是一本字典当然是这些 不是准确的值， 但它是好的
enough for this example and this would resemble something like if we scraped
足够 这个例子，这会 就像我们刮了一样
some website and pulled of the prices off or maybe someone emailed us a list of
一些网站和拉动的价格 关闭或者某人通过电子邮件向我们发送了一份 的
stocks that they were interested in and wanted us to make some program for it this of course would be an example of
他们感兴趣的股票和 希望我们 做一些方案，使 这当然是一个例子
what they gave us it's not sorted in any kind of way not alphabetical order not
他们给了我们什么，它没有任何排序 有点不按字母顺序排列
by price and of course it would be handy to have this nice and sorted so the
按价格，当然它会很方便 有这么好，排序所以
first thing I want to do is show you guys exactly we need to do to either get
我想做的第一件事就是告诉 你 球员 正是 我们需要做的，要么 得到
the minimum get the maximum or just like sort it and print it out so first what
最小值得到最大值或者就像 排序并打印出来，所以首先是什么
you need to do is actually use that zip function that we learned earlier and
你需要做的就是使用 那个拉链 我们之前学到的功能
what we're going to do is actually treat this as two lists a list of keys which is the name and the list of values now
我们要做的实际上是治疗 这两个列出了一个 键列表 是名称和值 现在 列表
if you guys don't know what zipping does um go watch my zip tutorial I made it
如果你们不知道 拉链的作用 嗯去看我的拉链教程我做到了
like two tutorials ago but a one sentence overview it takes two lists and it zips them together until a list of
像两个教程之前，但一个 句子概述它需要两个列表 和 它将它们拉到一起直到列表
tuples so now they're tied together and now we can do some pretty cool things to
元组 所以现在他们已经联系在一起， 现在我们可以做一些 非常 酷的事情了
them so again what we're going to do is we're
他们 所以我们要做的就是我们
going to use that zip function and I want to mention this you can not just
打算 使用那个zip功能 和我 想要提到 这个你不能只是
sort a dictionary by default but you can sort a zipped list since it is a list
默认排序字典，但你 可以 排序压缩列表，因为它是一个列表
now whenever python sorts things it looks at the first element in that list
现在每当 python对它进行排序时 查看该列表 中的 第一个元素
so remember whenever you zip a list you give it to lists which in this case is
所以每当你压缩列表时都要记得 将它列在这种情况下的列表中
the prices or the name and you time together so why am I saying this I just
价格或名称和 你的时间 我一起为什么 这样 说呢？
said that well it's actually really important because the item or the list that you've thrown first is how it's
说实际上真的很好 重要的是因为项目或 列表 你首先抛出的是它是怎么回事
going to sort it by so if you throw in the prices first your result is going to
如果你投入，那就去排序吧 价格第一 的结果是要
be sorted by prices if you throw in the names first is going to be sorted by
如果你投入， 按 价格 排序 名字首先按照排序
names in other words alphabetical order so let's say that we actually want to
换句话说，按字母顺序排列 的名字 所以我们说 我们真的 想要
sort these by the prices remember technically these are called the keys
按价格排序这些 从技术上讲，这些被称为键
and these are called the values so the first item we zip is going to be the
这些被称为价值所以 我们拉链的第一项 将是
value so stocks values that's the first list were thrown in all the blue stuff
价值因此股票 价值是第一个 列表被扔进了所有蓝色的东西
the second one is just going to be stocks
第二个是 只是要 个股
and keys right there so now what we have is pretty much a nice list that zipped
并且钥匙就在那里， 所以现在我们有了 几乎是 一个不错的清单压缩
together and we can perform any function that we would on any other list so let's
在一起，我们可以执行 任何功能 我们会在任何其他名单上这样让我们
just go ahead and get the minimum value of this list by taking this and thrown
继续前进，获得最低价值 通过这个和抛出这个列表
it in men and there we go so what this is going to do is it's
它在男人和我们去 所以这是怎么回事呢
going to get the minimum value of this nice zip to list now actually just want
要得到 这样 的最小值 好拉链列表现在实际上只是想要
to print out that value so that is how we're constructing that and I know I
打印出那个 值，这 就是如何 我们正在构建它，我知道我
kind of build it inside out but I just wanted to break it down you know not
有点建造它，但我只是 想要打破它， 你不知道
kind of like rap game break it down but yeah that's how it works so let's run
有点像说唱游戏打破了 但是 是的， 它是如何工作所以 让我们 运行
this and check it out so again it gives us thirty nine twenty-eight yahoo now
这一点，并检查出来，所以它再次给 我们三十九二十八雅虎吧
again the thing I want to point out is that even though the zip list consists
我想要指出的是 即使邮政编码包含在内
of two values it's sorted it or gave us the minimum price because the value of a
两个值的分类或 给我们 最低价格因为a的价值
dictionary is the second element so that's why it sipped together got the minimum and it printed it out now of
词典是 第二元素 ，以便 这就是为什么它一起喝了 最小，它现在打印出来
course the max is just really easy change min to max run that bad boy boom
当然，最大限度 非常简单 改变最小到最大运行那个坏男孩的繁荣
roast the next thing you know you got the max price pretty freaking sweet now
烤下你知道的下一件事 最高价格相当 现在 吓坏 甜
of course if you want this sorted you guys want like the third easiest thing
当然，如果你想要这样排序你 人们想要第三个最简单的事情
in the world change that max to sorted and now let's go ahead and run this Oh
在世界上 ，将最大值改为排序 现在让我们继续吧哦
mg Bucky check it out you just sorted an entire dictionary really really easily
毫克 Bucky看看你刚刚排序 了 整本字典真的很容易
so again now you can see kind of how this entire um as if the list is
如此反复，现在你可以看到 怎么 样 的 整个嗯好像是列表
constructed by a set of values in keys and of course the reason that it's
由键中的一组值构成 当然是它的原因
sorting by the price is because we threw values and first so it goes from minimum
按价格排序是因为我们扔了 价值和第一， 所以 它从最小
to maximum Yahoo being the cheapest and Google being the most expensive if we
最大雅虎是最便宜 ， 如果我们 谷歌是最贵的
ever wanted to sort it by the name all we have to do is change this the key
曾经想用所有的名字对它进行排序 我们要做的就是改变这个关键
these and this the values and what this is going to do is it's going to zip it together a little bit differently
这些和这个价值观和这个 要做的就是拉链 一点点不同
flip-flop the two around but you still get a nice sorted dictionary now in
翻转 两个但你仍然 现在得到一个很好的排序字典
alphabetical order so you guys are now experts on how to get the minimum
字母顺序， 所以你们现在 如何获得最低限度的专家
maximum and make a nice sorted dictionary check this out it's pretty
最大， 并做出一个很好的排序 字典检查这个很漂亮
much all one simple line of code Python would be really nice if they have
很多所有简单 的 代码 行 Python 如果有的话会非常好的
built-in way but you know it was easy enough so thank you guys for watching
内置的方式，但你知道这很容易 够了 ，谢谢你们 观看
and I'll see you guys in the next video
我会在下一个视频中看到你们